(Sheldon:)I've always found that
an inappropriate slur.
Chickens are not at all timid.
(Sheldon:)In fact, when I was young,
my neighbor's chicken got loose...
(Sheldon:)...and chased me up the big elm tree
in front of our house.
(Raj:)-Chickens can't climb trees.
-Thank God.
(Howard:)Okay, I believe a chicken made you
his bitch.
(Howard:)The cricket thing, I don't buy. Bet me.
(Sheldon:)Fair enough.
What stakes do you propose?
(Howard:)I will put up
my Fantastic Four Number 48...
(Howard:)...first appearance of Silver Surfer...
(Howard:)...against your Flash 123,
the classic "Flash of Two Worlds" issue.
(Sheldon:)All right, you have a wager.
(Howard:)Hmm.
(Leonard:)Great.
Now, how are you gonna settle it? Hmm?
(Raj:)There is no way to determine the species
of the cricket without examining it.